utrend.tv 2017-06-24

# uTrend.tv Privacy Policy

### uTrend.tv values your privacy and does not share personal information with 3rd parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this website other than to analyze and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies. 

**You can[opt to turn off the use of cookies at anytime](http://www.wikihow.com/Disable-Cookies) by changing settings in your web browser.**

Examples of data collected from visitors to this site include: 

1\. Google Analytics is used analyze traffic. This service is used to collect information such as the following from visitors: 

Internet Protocol addresses (IP)   
visitor location (town/state/country)   
Type of web browser   
Date and time stamp   
Referring and exit pages   
Number of clicks on links 

No personally identifiable information is collected by these services (i.e., no names or other personal information). 

2\. uTrend.tv uses one service to serve advertisements, Lijit Networks. Lijit Networks uses cookies to help them tailor ads to individual user interests. I have no access to or control over these cookies as they are served by a third party. Below are additional details about Lijit Networks service: 

Lijit Networks is a third-party ad server that provides ads relevant to user interests.   
You can find [Lijit's opt-out policy here.](http://www.lijit.com/choices)

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on December 1, 2013. 

Contact: utrendtv@gmail.com
